Jaguar Jung

qual95@berkeley.edu | 909.461.0034 | Fullerton, CA

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

Software Engineer with 2 years working experience in full-stack technologies along with an academic background in cognitive science and computer science. Currently focused on application scalability and performance at a business level as well as translating those efforts into deliverable products.

- Languages: English, Korean, Japanese
- Work Eligibility: Authorized to work in US without restrictions.

Core Technologies:

Languages: Java, Javascript/ES6&7, Python, SQL, HTML/CSS

Tools: React, Redux, Gatsby, Node, Spring, Hibernate, NPM, Git, GraphQL, VSCode/Eclipse

EDUCATION

University of California, Berkeley

Bachelor of Arts, Coginitive Science - Computer Modeling

Study Abroad: Doshisha University, Japan

Cal E-Sports Team Manager: League of Legends 2015 - 2016

<u>Computer Science Coursework</u>: Structure & Interpretation of Computer Programs, Data Structures, Discrete Mathematics & Probability theory, User Experience & Design, Data Visualization

WORK EXPERIENCE

Infosys Limited, Associate

Dec 2018 - Present

Graduated: Aug 2018

Full-Stack Java Developer - Client: American Express

- Analyzed codebase for defect-prone back-end architecture and initiated collaboration to restructure for high-performing stability and scalability, reducing future defect quantity & fix time by 50%.
- Contributed to complete software lifecycle through design, development, testing, and maintenance.
- Streamlined development onboarding through creation of documentation covering use of dev tools, app & database structure and functionality, and team resources, cutting down onboarding time by 70%.

HireClout, Web Development Intern

May 2016 - Aug 2016

• Transformed legacy features to support cross-platform and cross-device accessibility using CSS flexbox and media queries, improving 30% of code base for future stability.

PROJECTS

San Francisco Recidivism Data Dashboard

Client: San Francisco Justice Department

• Web based data visualization tool using Tableau to produce navigable data trends for legal progress regarding SF's recidivism issue.

League of Legends ARAM Statistics Application

React-based application featuring GraphQL API handling and character-driven build generation.

Portfolio Website

• Template-based website built with Gatsby, GraphQL, and Styled Components to showcase projects

^{**}Additional experience: Designer & Consultant at UC Berkeley 3D Makerspace (2015-2017), Professional Tournament Operations Staff at Next Generation E-Sports(2018)